<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hubspot on Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</title>
    <link>https://integrationagent.com/categories/hubspot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hubspot on Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Integration Agent 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 06:24:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://integrationagent.com/categories/hubspot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need SSL to Accept Payments and How to Setup SSL Certificate on HubSpot Website</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/setup-ssl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 06:24:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/setup-ssl</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;What makes a great online store? It used to be that mobile optimization,
great content, and responsiveness alone were enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, part of the process that you must accomplish when developing an
online store is determining how to secure online experiences of your
customers. If you’re new to online stores, you might get confused on SSL
certificates as a primary component of the web security process. You may
have tons of queries such as: what it is, how it works and more
important, how to set it up on your HubSpot website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article we break it down for you so that you
understand what SSL is, why you need it on your website and how to set
it up on your online store. Let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-ssl&#34;&gt;What is SSL?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL is an acronym for Secure Sockets Layer. In some instances, it’s
called the TSL (Transport Security Layer). SSL is simply a protocol that
encrypts transactions between a client application (a browser) and the
online store server. Simply put: SSL protects the sensitive information
such as credit card details—by making them private and confidential—from
being stolen by malicious users over the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL uses an encryption algorithm that ensures that each message being
exchanged on the web passes integrity test before being transmitted. If
the integrity test fails—due to corruption or an unexpected alteration
by malicious users—then such a transaction doesn’t proceed to successful
conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For you to enhance the security of online transactions, you should
obtain an SSL certificate that’s relevant for that domain. The
certificate will apply the encryption algorithms for all the
transactions that take place between customers and your online store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL is visible to users in several ways in the website address bar:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lock icon in the browser bar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The website address starting with https://
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/why-ssl/ssl_icon.png&#34;/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-is-ssl-certificate-vital-for-accepting-payments&#34;&gt;Why is SSL certificate vital for accepting payments?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As online mercantile, it’s your primary responsibility to ensure that
the information being exchanged over your online store—which you collect
from your customers—is protected at all costs. Here are reasons why you
should protect your customer’s sensitive information such as credit card
and personal information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-confidential-transactions&#34;&gt;1. Confidential Transactions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of any SSL is to transmit sensitive information
with an encrypted connection. Your customers must be assured that their
private data such as usernames, passwords and credit card numbers are
not revealed to malicious attackers while they are making online
payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-customer-s-trust&#34;&gt;2. Customer’s Trust&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of online shoppers are very choosy when it comes making
online payments. Therefore, it’s your duty to convince them their
privacy is guaranteed so that they trust your business and your
products. An SSL enabled online store improves customer’s trust to your
business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-set-up-an-ssl-certificate-on-a-hubspot-website&#34;&gt;How to set up an SSL certificate on a HubSpot website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have 4 options here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-buy-ssl-add-on-from-hubspot&#34;&gt;1. Buy SSL add-on from HubSpot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pricing range is $100-$600 per month. &lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hubspot.com/products/website/ssl&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/why-ssl/hubspot_ssl.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-install-certificate-on-your-server&#34;&gt;2. Install certificate on your server&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you host your website not on HubSpot, but for example Wordpress on your own server, then you can buy a certificate from any major certificate authorities or get a free one from &lt;a href=&#34;https://letsencrypt.org/&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt&lt;/a&gt;.
Then, you&amp;rsquo;d need to install it on your server, the installation process depends on your web server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-flexible-ssl-from-cloudflare&#34;&gt;3. Flexible SSL from CloudFlare&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this option you&amp;rsquo;ll need to move your domain to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cloudflare.com/&#34;&gt;CloudFlare&lt;/a&gt; and activate &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cloudflare.com/ssl/&#34;&gt;Flexible SSL&lt;/a&gt;.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve buying and installing SSL certificate, but your visitors will still see the SSL icon and https:// in the address bar.
Downside of this method is that it encrypts connection only between your site visitors and CloudFlare, but not from CloudFlare and your server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-depositfix-with-encrypted-subdomain&#34;&gt;4. DepositFix with encrypted subdomain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://depositfix.com&#34;&gt;DepositFix&lt;/a&gt; is a shopping cart created especially for HubSpot. You can get a free subdomain on your domain (e.g. payment.yourdomain.com) for payment form.
It&amp;rsquo;s still your domain, so buyers can be sure they pay to the right company plus you get fully 128-bit encrypted connection between browser and server.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HubSpot’s Analytic Tools That You Should Be Using besides the Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2016-07-30-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 06:23:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2016-07-30-analytics/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that the biggest challenge facing digital marketers today
is measuring how effective their marketing strategies is. While the role
of digital marketing in an enterprise can’t be overemphasized, it’s
important to evaluate the effectiveness of a marketing campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this blog, I’m certain that you may be confused
between going out for web analytics or marketing analytics. Before you
begin evaluating the effectiveness of your marketing campaign it’s vital
to distinguish between web and marketing analytics. So, what’s the
difference?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-07-30-analytics/image1.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, web analytics—what’s commonly known as Google analytics—measures
web metrics such as traffic, the bounce rate, page load times and unique
visitors. It provides you with insights on how prospects use your
website, how they get there, and measures that you can take to make them
visit again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, web analytics can also inform you which areas of your website
are performing well, and what you can do to improve them. These measures
are important for search rankings. If you want your website to rank
higher on Google (and any search engine) then you must ensure that your
website is not only responsive but also secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-about-marketing-analytics&#34;&gt;What about marketing analytics?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing analytics deals with measuring metrics such as visitor
traffic, the number of leads, and sales that come about as a result of a
digital marketing campaign. Put simply, marketing analytics are people
driven which features the prospects, leads, and customers while web
analytics deals with the responsiveness of the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know you’re thinking, “Between web analytics and marketing analytics,
which one comes first?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a tough question. However, both analytics are essential for your
website. Your website or blog won’t promote your bottom line if there
are no visitors or prospects. Therefore, the first strategy that you
should craft is search engine optimization. Measuring the readiness of
your website with regard to search engine optimization is what web
analytics is about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, you want to know how many prospects have visited your
website and how many have converted to leads and customers. This is a
critical component for measuring the success of your marketing campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth be told—majority of marketers have concentrated on web analytics
as opposed to marketing analytics. Here’s a fact, even if you spend so
many hours going through the data using Google analytic tools, you’ll
never comprehend the success of your marketing efforts unless you
embrace marketing analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s is how HubSpot’s marketing analytics can help you promote your
bottom line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-you-ll-integrate-your-marketing-efforts-across-multiple-channels&#34;&gt;#1: You’ll integrate your marketing efforts across multiple channels&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking out for a solid analytic system that can help you
integrate several channels, then look no further than HubSpot’s
marketing analytics. With HubSpot’s marketing analytic tools, you’ll be
in a position to determine how each individual channel—such as social
media, email marketing, and blogging—are performing. If you want to find
out which channel is generating more leads, then the HubSpot’s marketing
analytics tools will give you that report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-it-s-people-focused&#34;&gt;#2: It’s people-focused&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While web analytics focusses on page view reports to determine the
responsiveness of the website, marketing analytics is people-focused. If
you’re interested in knowing how a particular prospect came to find out
about your website, then HubSpot’s marketing analytics can tell you all
this and much more. As a matter of fact, marketing analytics provides
you with very powerful intelligence to grow your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-it-measures-sales&#34;&gt;#3: It measures sales&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your website may be efficient in lead generation. But the question is
…&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;are the leads converting to customers and making money for your
business?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; HubSpot marketing analytics can help you tell whether the
leads are converting into customers or not if you integrate it with
other sales channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowing whether your individual marketing campaign initiatives are
contributing to the bottom line is a surefire way of finding which
channels you should focus on. If you find out that your blog is the one
which is effective or social media, then you’ll be in a position to
craft strategies that optimize such a channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-it-s-superior-in-lead-tracking&#34;&gt;#4: It’s superior in lead tracking&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HubSpot’s COS marketing analytic tool provides superior lead tracking
when compared to Google analytics. This is because a marketer can
differentiate the traffic sources by segmenting them into locations
where they are coming from and their convenient geographical times for
accessing the content. This is essential in helping to further
understand buyer persona profiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, you can even track the activities of your prospects
when you the “Contacts” tools using their IP addresses. This makes the
HubSpot’s COS a superior tool from conversion rate point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there you have it. In a nutshell, your blog needs to not only
embrace best practices that enhance its SEO capabilities but also
marketing analytics that measures how well prospects are converting to
leads and customers. That’s why HubSpot’s marketing analytics is
essential for your marketing efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 HubSpot’s COS Best Tools that Can Power Your Social Media Strategies</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/social-media-tools</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 07:20:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/social-media-tools</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Developing a website (and ultimately a blog) is the first step towards
reaching out to the majority of customers. However, expanding your
online capabilities to reach out to social media users can help you
promote your bottom line. It’s a fact that social media marketing has
revolutionized the whole of the marketing landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way the social media platforms can promote your bottom line is by
helping you to interact with your customers. When you go through the
tweets and Facebook updates, you’ll be in a position to understand your
customer base—what’s commonly known as persona profile in digital
marketing. Once you understand your persona profile, you’ll be in a
position to craft strategies that address their needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a marketer, you should look out for the best tools that can help
power your social media marketing strategies. In “5 HubSpot’s COS Best
Tools that Can Power Your Social Media Strategies” we explore some of
the best marketing automation tools that can help power your social
media marketing strategies. Let’s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hubspot-s-tools-for-enhanced-social-media-marketing&#34;&gt;HubSpot’s tools for enhanced social media marketing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the best 5 tools that you can use on your HubSpot for enhanced
social media marketing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-social-media-inbox&#34;&gt;#1: Social Media Inbox&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-06-26-hubspot-social/image1.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you share tons of content on social media platforms, remembering
login information for all your clients can be a herculean task. Instead
of logging in manually to each of your social media platforms (Facebook,
Twitter, Google + and Instagram), the HubSpot’s Social Inbox can help
you organize these accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HubSpot’s Social Inbox is a powerful and intelligent social media
tool that connects to your entire contacts in the database and merges
them with social media interactions in your organization. When you use
this tool, you will be in a position to not only publish to all your
social media platform accounts, but you also monitor various
interactions with any customer in the database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, you’ll also automate the process of setting up your social
Inbox which can send you alerts and other push notifications when one of
the leads mentions your competitor on social media platforms. With these
alerts, you may respond directly with a link to the blog article so that
you demonstrate that your organization can offer better services
compared to your opponent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-social-monitoring&#34;&gt;#2: Social Monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-06-26-hubspot-social/image2.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An effective digital marketing strategy is one that allows a marketer to
connect with customers at a personalized level. Remember, understanding
your buyer persona profile is key to crafting strategies that creates
products/services that address their needs. When you incorporate the
HubSpot’s Social media monitoring tool, you’ll be able to listen to
Twitter conversations that are relevant to the growth of your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, the Social Monitoring tool helps you to track all the
Twitter messages, follow all the contact lists, and respond to all your
social media updates. In fact, you can now create streams and interact
with all your prospects, leads and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-social-media-publishing&#34;&gt;#3: Social Media Publishing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-06-26-hubspot-social/image3.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HubSpot’s Social Publishing tool allows you to post to all the
social media accounts in your organization. Remember sharing the content
with your prospects, leads and customers is one way to generate traffic
on your blog or website. Therefore, any social media marketing strategy
must involve content sharing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this tool, you can attach links to all your blog posts, images,
landing pages and other types of content. By attaching links to all the
content you’re creating, you can promote your social media content to
all your leads and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-social-media-reporting&#34;&gt;#4: Social Media Reporting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-06-26-hubspot-social/image4.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve scheduled and published your social media content. You’ve gone
ahead to engage with your social media followers. So, what next? You
need to evaluate the effectiveness of your marketing campaign. Social
media reporting can help your measure how your marketing efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, you may want to compare the social media activities
between the current month and the previous month for different social
media platforms. Also, finding out which social media platform is
outperforming others. Fortunately, the HubSpot’s Social Media Reporting
can help you evaluate the effectiveness of your marketing efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-social-media-settings&#34;&gt;#5: Social Media Settings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/2016-06-26-hubspot-social/image5.png&#34; class=&#34;blog-image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Different social media platforms require different publishing schedules.
For instance, Facebook may require fewer publications of the same
content on a given day compared to the Twitter. As a marketer, it’s
important to distinguish these publishing schedules. The HubSpot’s
Social Media Settings can help you manage all your social media accounts
and their different publishing schedules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even before you start using your HubSpot’s social media tools; it’s
important that you connect all your social media channels to your
HubSpot COS. Since each social media platform will require different
interactions with HubSpot, it’s important that you set up your HubSpot
COS before starting to create and publish content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;putting-it-all-together&#34;&gt;Putting it all together&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A well-crafted digital marketing strategy must involve social media
marketing. Therefore finding the best tools that can help you manage
your social media content is vital to the success of your marketing
efforts. That’s why you need to incorporate HubSpot’s social media tools
such as Social Inbox, Publishing, Monitoring, Reporting and Settings to
attain your bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ultimate Tips That Can Help You to Manage Your HubSpot Account</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-15-4-ultimate-tips-that-can-help-you-to-manage-your-hubspot-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-15-4-ultimate-tips-that-can-help-you-to-manage-your-hubspot-account/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The task of organizing a HubSpot portal can be daunting, especially if you’re a newbie. This is because you’ve just begun to figure out how the platform works without the knowledge of how to get the maximum gains of the portal.  If you knew how to organize your HubSpot Account, then you could save a great deal of time when using this amazing inbound marketing software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a marketer who has little time, or you simply don’t have the resources to help you explore what features are found in your HubSpot account, then it’s high time that you learned how to organize your HubSpot account to get the maximum benefits of inbound marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In “4 Ultimate Tips That Can Help You to Organize Your HubSpot Account”, we unveil practices that you can use to help you have an organized HubSpot account that delivers maximum benefits for your company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-for-managing-a-hubspot-account&#34;&gt;Best Practices for managing a HubSpot Account&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-54&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-644x768.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;How to Manage HubSpot Account&#34; width=&#34;588&#34; height=&#34;701&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-644x768.jpg 644w, https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-252x300.jpg 252w, https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account.jpg 808w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 588px) 100vw, 588px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the best practices for managing your HubSpot account for your business bottom line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Learn social media monitoring capability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your HubSpot’s COS promotes social media marketing—marketing strategy that is built on social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter. So, knowing how to track the conversations that takes place between your social media profile and that of potential customers is vital in helping you to save time—while providing greater insights on which types of social messages work and that ones are not successful in marketing your products/services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on the goal you’d like to achieve with your social media strategy—whether it’s improving your relationship with clients or increasing website traffic—you should learn how to organize your HubSpot account. Learn how to categorize your social media contacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s one thing that HubSpot can help you in social media marketing, then it is helping you to categorize your social media contacts. In fact, you can segment each communication from your clients by customizing each communication in different categories in an effective and efficient manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Learn how to organize the page performance tool&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve put a lot of time and resources in fine-tuning and promoting your HubSpot website/blog. It’s now time to see the results of your hard work. One way of measuring the results is through the page performance tool. Learning how to organize this tool can help you discover whether your inbound marketing strategy is working or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you navigate on your HubSpot website to the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Page Performance tool&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” that’s located under the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” tab, you’ll come across the various statistics for total views, keywords, and inbound links.  These statistics will change depending on the period that you’ve selected—today, this week, or previous month.  If you want to analyze the results on a weekly basis, or monthly basis, then you can use this tool. The statistics that you get from these reports are important in helping you to find out whether your marketing strategy is working or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Learn to segment your contacts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inbound marketing strategy is dependent on sending the &lt;em&gt;right content&lt;/em&gt; to the &lt;em&gt;right contacts&lt;/em&gt; at an &lt;em&gt;appropriate time&lt;/em&gt;. You wouldn’t want to send content that’s not relevant to your client as this may have adverse effects on your marketing strategy. Therefore, you should learn how to segment your contacts so that you only send the relevant information to the right customers or leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, your HubSpot’s COS has the integrated functionalities that can help you segment and organize your contacts. You can use the static method of holding the contact lists or the efficient method. A fixed contacts list is useful if you’d like to make a follow-up information for those leads that signed for your promotional e-book or whitepaper at a particular time or place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, a quick contact list—a list that continuously updates with each new contact that’s added who meets the list criteria—is a useful tool that can help you stay connected with your clients. This is because, this list will always have an updated contacts—whether they are leads or customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Learn to manage your calendar well&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Planning to send posts—whether blog posts or social media posts—can be tedious and time-consuming. However, with a well-managed schedule, you can keep track of which type of content should be posted at what time to which groups of people.  For instance, you can use the HubSpot’s social media content calendar template to help you manage the social media posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a tool is important in helping you to manage your social media campaign as you scale up your social media marketing. Well, if you follow the four tips to the later, then you can maximize your HubSpot’s website for your business bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Dive into Why Your HubSpot CMS Is Slow</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-19-why-your-hubspot-cms-is-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-19-why-your-hubspot-cms-is-slow/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Do you know why your HubSpot marketing website has suddenly slowed down?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this—a visitor who’s interested in your product enters your URL in her browser so that she can access more information about your products after finding your site on a search engine. But instead of your home page loading faster, your visitor has to keep waiting for your website pages to load slowly, one at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the implication of slow websites for your business?  Your client will simply lose the attention with your website. Regarding business, you’ll have lost a potential customer who’ll have brought in more loyal customers to your business. In a nutshell, the impact of conservative websites is huge when looked at from a business angle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, let’s dive in and find out why all of a sudden, your HubSpot marketing website is slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-your-hubspot-marketing-website-is-slow&#34;&gt;Why your HubSpot marketing website is slow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are factors that can contribute to a slow HubSpot marketing website:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-you-ve-not-optimized-images-on-your-website&#34;&gt;1: You’ve not optimized images on your website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using too many or too large images on your HubSpot CMS can tremendously slow down your website. This is because, as you increase the number and the size of images on your website, load time increases which degrades the performance of your HubSpot website. Your website should have only the optimized images that have been presented in the correct format and are of the right size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you optimize images on your HubSpot Website? As a rule of thumb, always apply the following tips when creating images for your website:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always crop the images that you place on your website to the correct size. For instance, if your website page is 600px wide, then you should resize your images properly so that they fits that page width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduce the color depth of your images to the lowest acceptable levels of the color depth will affect the load times and performance on the client’s browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For photos use JPG as your preferred image file format. For storing line drawings, text, and iconic graphics at a smaller file size PNG is a better choice. Avoid using BMP and TIFF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-unoptimized-css-or-javascript&#34;&gt;2: Unoptimized CSS or JavaScript&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your HubSpot website has a large code—it has additional spaces, line breaks, and indentations—then, you expect to have a slow website. If your CSS code has white spaces—which improves the readability of website code—then, there are high chances that it will slow down the performance of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should ensure that you compress your code to improve the performance of your website. If you want to compact your website code, you can GZIP your code. A GZIPed code significantly reduces the file size without affecting the images or video quality on your website. Here’s is how you can compact your website code:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always add the CSS and JavaScript to the external files as opposed to adding them inside your website This will ensure that these codes aren’t loaded wherever each page loads on a client browser, but they are only called whenever they’re required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always add the JS files to the footer of the web page where it’s possible. Placing the JS files at the footer of a web page ensures that they load in the background and don’t delay the web page that’s loading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look out for plugins that can compact the code on your HubSpot website. Tools such as YSlow—by Yahoo!, WebsiteTest.com—by Yottaa, Pingdom Website Speed Test can help you test the load times for your website to ensure its performance is within acceptable limits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-lack-of-browser-caching&#34;&gt;3: Lack of browser caching&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can reduce the load times for your website by storing commonly used website files—which include the html files, the CSS style sheets, the JavaScript scripts, as well as the graphic images— from your website on your clients’ browsers. In this case, you improve the load times by storing copies of your website images, your CSS, and JavaScript so that next time your client visits your website, his/her browser doesn’t have to load afresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that you should consider while using this feature is knowing the expiry time. Of course, the expiry time will depend on a couple of factors, chief among them being the different files that you’ll be caching and the restrictions that are defined by RFC’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-lack-of-plugin-optimization&#34;&gt;4: Lack of Plugin optimization&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a fact—plugins can help you to increase the functionalities of your HubSpot website. But too many plugins can slow down the performance of your website. In fact, if you use so many plugins that require many resources—such as the scripts and CSS—then such plugins are likely to perform complex operations that can degrade the performance of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, you should use plugins sparingly on your website only when they are necessary.  Otherwise, leave them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-bottom-line&#34;&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A slow website leads to losses of potential customers who’ll have brought in more loyal customers to your business. Therefore, you should always strive to improve the load times and performance of your website. To improve the load times and performance of your website—so that it’s not slow—you have to optimize the images, optimize the codes, optimize browser catching and finally use the plugins sparingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the only way that you’ll make your slow HubSpot website or blog to have a more conversion process from prospects into loyal customers. What’s your take? Keep us posted.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>