<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</title>
    <link>https://integrationagent.com/categories/payments/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Integration Agent 2016</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://integrationagent.com/categories/payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need SSL to Accept Payments and How to Setup SSL Certificate on HubSpot Website</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/setup-ssl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 06:24:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/setup-ssl</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;What makes a great online store? It used to be that mobile optimization,
great content, and responsiveness alone were enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, part of the process that you must accomplish when developing an
online store is determining how to secure online experiences of your
customers. If you’re new to online stores, you might get confused on SSL
certificates as a primary component of the web security process. You may
have tons of queries such as: what it is, how it works and more
important, how to set it up on your HubSpot website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article we break it down for you so that you
understand what SSL is, why you need it on your website and how to set
it up on your online store. Let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-ssl&#34;&gt;What is SSL?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL is an acronym for Secure Sockets Layer. In some instances, it’s
called the TSL (Transport Security Layer). SSL is simply a protocol that
encrypts transactions between a client application (a browser) and the
online store server. Simply put: SSL protects the sensitive information
such as credit card details—by making them private and confidential—from
being stolen by malicious users over the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL uses an encryption algorithm that ensures that each message being
exchanged on the web passes integrity test before being transmitted. If
the integrity test fails—due to corruption or an unexpected alteration
by malicious users—then such a transaction doesn’t proceed to successful
conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For you to enhance the security of online transactions, you should
obtain an SSL certificate that’s relevant for that domain. The
certificate will apply the encryption algorithms for all the
transactions that take place between customers and your online store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SSL is visible to users in several ways in the website address bar:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lock icon in the browser bar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The website address starting with https://
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/why-ssl/ssl_icon.png&#34;/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-is-ssl-certificate-vital-for-accepting-payments&#34;&gt;Why is SSL certificate vital for accepting payments?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As online mercantile, it’s your primary responsibility to ensure that
the information being exchanged over your online store—which you collect
from your customers—is protected at all costs. Here are reasons why you
should protect your customer’s sensitive information such as credit card
and personal information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-confidential-transactions&#34;&gt;1. Confidential Transactions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of any SSL is to transmit sensitive information
with an encrypted connection. Your customers must be assured that their
private data such as usernames, passwords and credit card numbers are
not revealed to malicious attackers while they are making online
payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-customer-s-trust&#34;&gt;2. Customer’s Trust&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of online shoppers are very choosy when it comes making
online payments. Therefore, it’s your duty to convince them their
privacy is guaranteed so that they trust your business and your
products. An SSL enabled online store improves customer’s trust to your
business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-set-up-an-ssl-certificate-on-a-hubspot-website&#34;&gt;How to set up an SSL certificate on a HubSpot website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have 4 options here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-buy-ssl-add-on-from-hubspot&#34;&gt;1. Buy SSL add-on from HubSpot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pricing range is $100-$600 per month. &lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hubspot.com/products/website/ssl&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/why-ssl/hubspot_ssl.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-install-certificate-on-your-server&#34;&gt;2. Install certificate on your server&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you host your website not on HubSpot, but for example Wordpress on your own server, then you can buy a certificate from any major certificate authorities or get a free one from &lt;a href=&#34;https://letsencrypt.org/&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt&lt;/a&gt;.
Then, you&amp;rsquo;d need to install it on your server, the installation process depends on your web server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-flexible-ssl-from-cloudflare&#34;&gt;3. Flexible SSL from CloudFlare&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this option you&amp;rsquo;ll need to move your domain to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cloudflare.com/&#34;&gt;CloudFlare&lt;/a&gt; and activate &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cloudflare.com/ssl/&#34;&gt;Flexible SSL&lt;/a&gt;.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve buying and installing SSL certificate, but your visitors will still see the SSL icon and https:// in the address bar.
Downside of this method is that it encrypts connection only between your site visitors and CloudFlare, but not from CloudFlare and your server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-depositfix-with-encrypted-subdomain&#34;&gt;4. DepositFix with encrypted subdomain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://depositfix.com&#34;&gt;DepositFix&lt;/a&gt; is a shopping cart created especially for HubSpot. You can get a free subdomain on your domain (e.g. payment.yourdomain.com) for payment form.
It&amp;rsquo;s still your domain, so buyers can be sure they pay to the right company plus you get fully 128-bit encrypted connection between browser and server.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences between Payment Gateway and a Merchant Account</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/payment-gateway-merchant-account</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 06:24:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/payment-gateway-merchant-account</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Virtually all businesses—from big-box retailers to Etsy merchants, from
trade show merchants to antique sellers—accept payments in the form of
credit cards. And here is the fact: more and more businesses are
accepting online payments in this fast-paced, ever-changing and complex
e-commerce industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re already accepting credit card payments from online sales, then
you must be at home with merchant accounts. However, if you’re a newbie
in e-commerce, then you must be grappling to learn about payment
gateways. So, what’s the difference between merchant accounts and
payment gateways?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-merchant-account&#34;&gt;What is a merchant account?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A merchant account is an online bank account that temporarily holds your
money once payment has been approved by a payment gateway. After a
successful payment, money will stay in your merchant account for a few
days (between 2 to 7 days) after which it will be transferred to your
real bank account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main types of merchant accounts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dedicated Merchant Account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggregate Merchant Account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;dedicated-merchant-account&#34;&gt;Dedicated Merchant Account&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A dedicated Merchant Account provides you with total control over your
funds. For every transaction that’s conducted, the merchant account
provider deducts processing fees and the rest of the money is deposited
into your business account. You can set up your account with payment
gateway systems such as Authorize.Net, PayLeap, and Blue Pay Processing
LLC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the actions that you can take while using a dedicated merchant
account are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debiting your account in case your customers make charge-back claims&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Correcting the errors in the transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking necessary actions in case there’s an evidence of fraudulent activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;aggregate-merchant-account&#34;&gt;Aggregate Merchant Account&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this type of account, the money that customers pay is pooled with
other companies. For you to open such an account, you must provide
details about your company and the type of products and services that
you’re dealing with. Since the amount of money in your account is pooled
with other companies, you don’t have exclusive control over the account.
In fact, you can’t negotiate the rates when using this account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-about-a-payment-gateway&#34;&gt;What about a payment gateway?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A payment gateway is an e-commerce application system that permits
credit card payments for e-commerce transactions, online retailing and
traditional brick and mortar transactions. When customers are buying
goods and services from your online store, they fill out their credit
card details during the checkout process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your online store will then send the credit card data that has been
entered during the checkout process to the payment gateway to authorize
the transaction and process the payment. During the processing, all the
payment gateway does is to verify whether the information customers have
submitted matches the data that’s available on the credit card. If they
match, then the payment is approved and money is then transferred from
the customer’s account to your merchant account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the popular payment gateways—that don’t require merchant
accounts—include PayPal, Stripe and Braintree Payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main feature of these payment gateways is that you will not need to
change bank accounts. Or, perform anything special for you to get up
running with the payments processing. Furthermore, it’s easier to
integrate these systems with your online store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But still, there are downsides too. First, there are higher transaction
charges that you’ll incur when using these payment systems. Second,
virtually all modern payment gateways always send customers to off-sites
while making payments. This often reduces the conversion rates for some
stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-which-option-is-right-for-your-business&#34;&gt;So, which option is right for your business?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merchant accounts have been with us for quite some time since the coming
on of credit cards. If you’re a retailer that sells primarily from the
brick and mortar stores, then setting up a merchant account can help you
increase your cash flows in the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the payment gateways are ideal for e-businesses and
other mobile retailers. When you use this payment gateway, the retailers
can easily enter and approve their credit card details from their mobile
devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;cta&#34;&gt;
	Which payment gateway has the smallest fees?

		&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.depositfix.com/calc/&#39;&gt;
			&lt;button class=&#34;button&#34; href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/&#34;&gt;Payment Gateways Fee Calculator&lt;/button&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;putting-it-together&#34;&gt;Putting it together&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding a payment gateway system or a merchant account to your online
store is a critical part of enhancing your business bottom line. When
you’re ready to accept payments, you can compete favorably in today’s
fast-paced and ever-evolving business environment. I hope this post has
been helpful in your search for the differences between payment gateways
and merchant accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>