<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</title>
    <link>https://integrationagent.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Integration Agent - Get the most out of your marketing automation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Integration Agent 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 08:51:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://integrationagent.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>smartforms</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/smartforms</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 08:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/smartforms</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/smartforms&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get HubSpot API key</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/how-to-get-hubspot-api-key</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/how-to-get-hubspot-api-key</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HubSpot API is required to get access to your HubSpot portal via API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get it, go to &amp;#8220;Integrations&amp;#8221;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone&#34; src=&#34;https://intagent.s3.amazonaws.com/s/HubSpot_API_Key_Manager_2016-01-24_20-58-25.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;262&#34; height=&#34;178&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, &amp;#8220;Get Your HubSpot API Key&amp;#8221;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone&#34; src=&#34;https://intagent.s3.amazonaws.com/s/Integrations_Home_2016-01-24_21-00-34.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;226&#34; height=&#34;352&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that you can view existing key or create a new one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to display custom error message in HubSpot form</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/custom-form-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/custom-form-message/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HubSpot form has native validation and error message display, but sometimes you need to display a validation message not just for each field, but for entire form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, HubSpot form API doesn&amp;#8217;t provide a callback for failed validation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But here is the workaround: we know that HS form inserts an element with an error message, so we can monitor that element after form being submitted:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre class=&#34;lang:default decode:true&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;

    hbspt.forms.create({
        formId: &#39;c3794ad3-f6a7-4c98-841d-98062636baab&#39;,
        portalId: &#39;1670983&#39;,
        onFormReady: function($form, ctx) {

            var errorMessage = &#34;Your Error Message&#34;;

            $form.find(&#34;input[type=&#39;submit&#39;]&#34;).click(function(){
                var sbmt = $(this);

                window.setTimeout(function(){
                    if($(&#34;.hs-error-msgs&#34;).length &amp;gt; 0){
                        //Put message on the top
                        $form.prepend(&#34;&amp;lt;div class=&#39;form-error-message&#39;&amp;gt;&#34; + errorMessage + &#34;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#34;)

                        //Put message on the bottom
                        sbmt.parent().prepend(&#34;&amp;lt;div class=&#39;form-error-message&#39;&amp;gt;&#34; + errorMessage + &#34;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#34;)
                    }else{
                        $form.find(&#34;.form-error-message&#34;).remove();
                    }

                //delay to make sure native hbspt form error already appeared
                }, 300);
            });
        }
    });
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;


&amp;lt;style&amp;gt;
    .form-error-message {
        color: #ff0000;
        font-weight: bold;
        padding: 15px 0px;
    }
&amp;lt;/style&amp;gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can display your message on top or on the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a working example of this kind of form:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This functionality will be included to the SmartForm plugin we are developing: &lt;a href=&#34;http://integrationagent.com/smartforms&#34;&gt;http://integrationagent.com/smartforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ultimate Tips That Can Help You to Manage Your HubSpot Account</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-15-4-ultimate-tips-that-can-help-you-to-manage-your-hubspot-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-15-4-ultimate-tips-that-can-help-you-to-manage-your-hubspot-account/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The task of organizing a HubSpot portal can be daunting, especially if you’re a newbie. This is because you’ve just begun to figure out how the platform works without the knowledge of how to get the maximum gains of the portal.  If you knew how to organize your HubSpot Account, then you could save a great deal of time when using this amazing inbound marketing software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a marketer who has little time, or you simply don’t have the resources to help you explore what features are found in your HubSpot account, then it’s high time that you learned how to organize your HubSpot account to get the maximum benefits of inbound marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In “4 Ultimate Tips That Can Help You to Organize Your HubSpot Account”, we unveil practices that you can use to help you have an organized HubSpot account that delivers maximum benefits for your company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-for-managing-a-hubspot-account&#34;&gt;Best Practices for managing a HubSpot Account&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-54&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-644x768.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;How to Manage HubSpot Account&#34; width=&#34;588&#34; height=&#34;701&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-644x768.jpg 644w, https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account-252x300.jpg 252w, https://integrationagent.com/img/How-to-Manage-HubSpot-Account.jpg 808w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 588px) 100vw, 588px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the best practices for managing your HubSpot account for your business bottom line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Learn social media monitoring capability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your HubSpot’s COS promotes social media marketing—marketing strategy that is built on social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter. So, knowing how to track the conversations that takes place between your social media profile and that of potential customers is vital in helping you to save time—while providing greater insights on which types of social messages work and that ones are not successful in marketing your products/services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on the goal you’d like to achieve with your social media strategy—whether it’s improving your relationship with clients or increasing website traffic—you should learn how to organize your HubSpot account. Learn how to categorize your social media contacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s one thing that HubSpot can help you in social media marketing, then it is helping you to categorize your social media contacts. In fact, you can segment each communication from your clients by customizing each communication in different categories in an effective and efficient manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Learn how to organize the page performance tool&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve put a lot of time and resources in fine-tuning and promoting your HubSpot website/blog. It’s now time to see the results of your hard work. One way of measuring the results is through the page performance tool. Learning how to organize this tool can help you discover whether your inbound marketing strategy is working or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you navigate on your HubSpot website to the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Page Performance tool&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” that’s located under the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” tab, you’ll come across the various statistics for total views, keywords, and inbound links.  These statistics will change depending on the period that you’ve selected—today, this week, or previous month.  If you want to analyze the results on a weekly basis, or monthly basis, then you can use this tool. The statistics that you get from these reports are important in helping you to find out whether your marketing strategy is working or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Learn to segment your contacts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inbound marketing strategy is dependent on sending the &lt;em&gt;right content&lt;/em&gt; to the &lt;em&gt;right contacts&lt;/em&gt; at an &lt;em&gt;appropriate time&lt;/em&gt;. You wouldn’t want to send content that’s not relevant to your client as this may have adverse effects on your marketing strategy. Therefore, you should learn how to segment your contacts so that you only send the relevant information to the right customers or leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, your HubSpot’s COS has the integrated functionalities that can help you segment and organize your contacts. You can use the static method of holding the contact lists or the efficient method. A fixed contacts list is useful if you’d like to make a follow-up information for those leads that signed for your promotional e-book or whitepaper at a particular time or place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, a quick contact list—a list that continuously updates with each new contact that’s added who meets the list criteria—is a useful tool that can help you stay connected with your clients. This is because, this list will always have an updated contacts—whether they are leads or customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Learn to manage your calendar well&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Planning to send posts—whether blog posts or social media posts—can be tedious and time-consuming. However, with a well-managed schedule, you can keep track of which type of content should be posted at what time to which groups of people.  For instance, you can use the HubSpot’s social media content calendar template to help you manage the social media posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a tool is important in helping you to manage your social media campaign as you scale up your social media marketing. Well, if you follow the four tips to the later, then you can maximize your HubSpot’s website for your business bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/products</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/products</guid>
      <description>

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;depositfix-payment-solution-for-hubspot&#34;&gt;DepositFix – Payment Solution for HubSpot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accept payments using your HubSpot forms and run marketing campaigns based on purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.depositfix.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.depositfix.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;smart-forms-for-hubspot&#34;&gt;Smart Forms for HubSpot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smart Forms for HubSpot can help you increase signup conversion by 17%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You probably know, that popup forms are very effective in terms of converting your visitors to subscribers, but at the same time they can be very annoying to users that can lead to a high bounce rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smart Forms provides a compromise of effective and user friendly way to increase forms conversion rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HubSpot native.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built specifically for HubSpot, you can use like any other module.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile ready&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slide in form, doesn’t block content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timed based appearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a user closes the form – it wouldn’t show up for the next 24 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a user submitted the form, the popup for this specific form will never be shown again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scroll-Based (in development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exit-Intent (in development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://integrationagent.com/smartforms&#34;&gt;Get SmartForms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;hubspot-api-java-client&#34;&gt;HubSpot API Java Client&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open Source library to work with HubSpot API written in Java.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;currently-implemented&#34;&gt;Currently implemented&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engagements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;maven-installation&#34;&gt;Maven Installation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;highlight highlight-text-xml&#34;&gt;
  &lt;pre class=&#34;lang:default decode:true &#34;&gt;&amp;lt;repositories&amp;gt;
    ...
    &amp;lt;repository&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;id&amp;gt;bintray&amp;lt;/id&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;url&amp;gt;http://dl.bintray.com/integrationagent/hubspot-java&amp;lt;/url&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;releases&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;enabled&amp;gt;true&amp;lt;/enabled&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/releases&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;snapshots&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;enabled&amp;gt;false&amp;lt;/enabled&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/snapshots&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;/repository&amp;gt;
    ...
&amp;lt;/repositories&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;dependencies&amp;gt;
    ...
    &amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;com.integrationagent&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;hubspot-java&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;0.1&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;/dependency&amp;gt;
    ...
&amp;lt;/dependencies&amp;gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/integrationagent/hubspot-java&#34;&gt;Fork on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Integrating Your HubSpot with Other CMS’s is Your Major Undoing</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-03-why-integrating-your-hubspot-with-other-cmss-is-your-major-undoing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-12-03-why-integrating-your-hubspot-with-other-cmss-is-your-major-undoing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We already covered techniques on &lt;a href=&#34;http://integrationagent.com/how-to-integrate-your-hubspot-with-other-cms/&#34;&gt;how to integrate HubSpot with the 3rd party CMSs&lt;/a&gt;. But let&amp;#8217;s discuss why it might be not a good idea to host your content outside of HubSpot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you craft a good content in the right context, you’ll attract the right visitors to your website, convert them into leads and close them into your loyal customers. In other words, content is like fuel that that powers any successful marketing strategy. Fortunately, this is what the HubSpot CMS is all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, there are two approaches that you can use to help integrate your traditional CMS with an inbound marketing strategy that will help pull people from one stage of a buyer’s decision to another. You can use the HubSpot’s COS (Content Optimization System)—a comprehensive internet inbound marketing platform—that integrates everything you should do to grow your online presence using one easy-to-use panel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or, you can integrate your traditional CMS with HubSpot’s Tracking Code if you’d like to exploit the inbound marketing strategy that’s presented in HubSpot COS. So, which approach is the best for your business? Should you just use the HubSpot’s COS or, should you integrate your traditional CMS with HubSpot’s tracking code?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog article, we highlight some of the demerits that the CMS’s that have been integrated with HubSpot’s tracking code over the HubSpot’s COS. This will help you make a decision as to whether you should remain with your traditional CMS that has been integrated with HubSpot’s tracking code or migrate to HubSpot COS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, let’s dive in and find out why the traditional CMS that has been integrated with HubSpot’s tracking code has been your major undoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;demerits-of-traditional-cms-s-that-have-been-integrated-with-hubspot-s-tracking-codes&#34;&gt;Demerits of traditional CMS’s that have been integrated with HubSpot’s tracking codes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the demerits of traditional CMS’s that have been integrated into HubSpot’s tracking codes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#1: They have sluggish designs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As technology evolves, you have to design your website that keeps up with the latest trends. For instance, you have to design websites or blogs that can easily be read on the tablets, the smartphones or other mobile devices, besides the desktop computer. Integrating a HubSpot’s tracking code with a traditional CMS may not produce a responsive design that produce a website that are accessible on the tablets, the smartphones or other mobile devices and the desktop computers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the HubSpot’s COS is completely responsive, since it automates the process instead of having to code the website for responsiveness. This means that you’ll not require any CSS or HTML knowledge to create a website that is customized for tablets, smartphones or other mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#2: They are slow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a fact: HubSpot has been ranked first in speed compare to other traditional CMS’s such as Joomla, WordPress or Drupal. So, if you want your website to have improved speeds, then you should consider migrating to HubSpot COS. This will even promote your web presence since most search engines have incorporated website speeds in their search algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#3: They don’t deliver targeted content&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The traditional CMS’s can only help you to publish, edit and modify any content that you’d like your visitors, leads and customers to access. However, a good content marketing strategy should revolve around not just delivering content, but delivery the &lt;em&gt;right content&lt;/em&gt;, at the &lt;em&gt;appropriate time&lt;/em&gt; and in the &lt;em&gt;right context&lt;/em&gt; to your visitors, leads or customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HubSpot COS can help your firm to convey the &lt;em&gt;right content&lt;/em&gt;, at the &lt;em&gt;appropriate time&lt;/em&gt; and in the &lt;em&gt;right context&lt;/em&gt; to your visitors, leads or customers. Such a good content—content that’s created based on the buyer’s journey lifecycle—will be targeted to specific groups of people that you’d like to access in the niche market. Therefore, if you’re not using the HubSpot’s COS, then you’re missing out on attracting the right visitors, the right leads and customers to your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#4: Cumbersome update and editing features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integrating HubSpot’s tracking code and traditional CMS’s may create a website or blog that’s tough to update and edit. This is because blog posts, website, and social media may be in different panels. When you use the HubSpot COS, you’ll have an amazing control panel that lets you add new blog posts, edit your posts and publish them on social media platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be doing all these from one central control panel as opposed to traditional CMS’s that have been integrated into HubSpot’s tracking codes. So, there you have it. Keep us posted in case you have any queries.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Integrate Your HubSpot with other CMSs</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-20-how-to-integrate-your-hubspot-with-other-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-20-how-to-integrate-your-hubspot-with-other-cms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Are you finding it difficult to integrate your blog or website with HubSpot marketing software? Are you worried that you’ll lose on HubSpot’s inbound marketing capabilities because your website is using Joomla, Drupal or WordPress CMS? Well, if you’ve been asking yourself these questions, then you’ve just landed on the right page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that the HubSpot’s inbound marketing strategy—which is provided in a marketing software—can help you attract visitors to your website, convert them into leads and eventually persuade them to be your loyal customers. If you have a HubSpot marketing software, then you are assured that you’ll not only have increased online presence but also increased conversion rates from visitors to leads who’ll eventually turn into customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many businesses have used the HubSpot’s inbound marketing strategy to grow their business by turning their websites and blogs into magnets—which engages their prospects with the appropriate landing pages, the calls to action and personalized emails that target the right customers. But here’s the fact: most firms would like to use their own CMS—whether Joomla, Drupal or WordPress—besides the HubSpot’s marketing software even though HubSpot has its own CMS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, how do you integrate your HubSpot’s marketing software with Joomla, Drupal, Magento or WordPress blog or website? Good question. In this article, we walk you through the process of linking your blog or website that’s been developed using either with Joomla, Drupal, Magento or WordPress with HubSpot’s marketing software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But first, let’s understand the basics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-basics-of-linking-hubspot-with-cms-s&#34;&gt;The Basics of Linking HubSpot with CMS’s&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re hosting your website or blog using either Joomla, Drupal, Magento or WordPress and you’d like to exploit the advanced analytics that are provided by HubSpot, then you have to install the HubSpot Tracking Code. Ideally, a HubSpot tracking code helps your website or blog to capture the HubSpot analytics that helps you to understand your marketing data better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell the primary aims of this code include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determining how well your website or blog is generating the traffic and the leads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What’s required for you can do to improve your website or blog traffic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing you with erudite lead intelligence that can help you to convert more website leads into loyal customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re using either Joomla, Drupal or WordPress website or blog, then you should know how to install this tracking code manually on your website. Here’s how:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-installing-hubspot-tracking-code-on-wordpress&#34;&gt;#1: Installing HubSpot Tracking Code on WordPress&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s the easiest one, just install  &amp;#8220;HubSpot Tracking Code&amp;#8221; plugin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture3.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;wp-image-34 size-full aligncenter&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture3.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture3&#34; width=&#34;964&#34; height=&#34;461&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture3.png 964w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture3-300x143.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture3-644x308.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 964px) 100vw, 964px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-installing-hubspot-tracking-code-on-joomla&#34;&gt;#2: Installing HubSpot Tracking Code on Joomla&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the steps that you should follow when installing the HubSpot’s tracking code on Joomla websites:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin by copying the HubSpot Tracking Code. For you to copy the HubSpot Tracking code, navigate to the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” menu on your HubSpot software.         &lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture6.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-medium wp-image-37&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture6-255x300.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture6&#34; width=&#34;255&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture6-255x300.png 255w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture6.png 439w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 255px) 100vw, 255px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reports Settings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;”. Next, copy the copy the HubSpot Tracking Code to the clipboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture7.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;wp-image-38 size-full aligncenter&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture7.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture7&#34; width=&#34;983&#34; height=&#34;551&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture7.png 983w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture7-300x168.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture7-644x361.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 983px) 100vw, 983px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the option that you’d like to use to integrate your tracking code to your website. Ideally, there are two options that you can use: through the installed Joomla extension and using the “index.php” file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you decide to use the first option—using Joomla extension— then, select the extension of your choice from the Joomla Extension Directory and paste in your HubSpot Tracking Code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you decide to use the “index.php” file option then, log into your Joomla website as an Administrator. Locate the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Extensions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” and select the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Template Manager&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture8.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;wp-image-39 aligncenter&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture8.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture8&#34; width=&#34;800&#34; height=&#34;171&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture8.png 1451w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture8-300x64.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture8-644x138.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toggle the view on “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Templates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” and select the template of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture10.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;wp-image-41 size-full aligncenter&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture10.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture10&#34; width=&#34;758&#34; height=&#34;514&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture10.png 758w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture10-300x203.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture10-644x437.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t forget to save the changes to the “index.php” file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-installing-hubspot-tracking-code-on-drupal-websites&#34;&gt;#3: Installing HubSpot Tracking Code on Drupal websites&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the steps that you should follow when installing the HubSpot’s tracking code on Drupal websites:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copy HubSpot Tracking code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log into your Drupal website as an Administrator. On the Administrator’s Dashboard, Click on the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Structure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” that’s located in the top menu of the Dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blocks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture11.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-42 size-full&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture11.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture11&#34; width=&#34;758&#34; height=&#34;430&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture11.png 758w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture11-300x170.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture11-644x365.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add Block&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” link.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture12.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-43 size-full&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture12.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture12&#34; width=&#34;889&#34; height=&#34;407&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture12.png 889w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture12-300x137.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture12-644x295.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 889px) 100vw, 889px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in the following settings for the new block that you’ve just created:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture131.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-46&#34; src=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture131.png&#34; alt=&#34;Picture13&#34; width=&#34;945&#34; height=&#34;1448&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture131.png 945w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture131-196x300.png 196w, https://integrationagent.com/img/Picture131-644x987.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 945px) 100vw, 945px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block title: Indicate the title of your block.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block description. Indicate the description of your block.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block body. Here’s is where you paste your HubSpot Tracking Code that you copied to the clipboard above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Text format. Select “Full HTML”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Region settings: Select &amp;#8216;Footer&amp;#8217; as your default theme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visibility settings. You can skip this setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there you have it. You should be in a position to integrate your HubSpot with any CMS now. Keep us posted. We’ll be happy to respond to your queries.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Dive into Why Your HubSpot CMS Is Slow</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-19-why-your-hubspot-cms-is-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/blog/2015-11-19-why-your-hubspot-cms-is-slow/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Do you know why your HubSpot marketing website has suddenly slowed down?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this—a visitor who’s interested in your product enters your URL in her browser so that she can access more information about your products after finding your site on a search engine. But instead of your home page loading faster, your visitor has to keep waiting for your website pages to load slowly, one at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the implication of slow websites for your business?  Your client will simply lose the attention with your website. Regarding business, you’ll have lost a potential customer who’ll have brought in more loyal customers to your business. In a nutshell, the impact of conservative websites is huge when looked at from a business angle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, let’s dive in and find out why all of a sudden, your HubSpot marketing website is slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-your-hubspot-marketing-website-is-slow&#34;&gt;Why your HubSpot marketing website is slow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are factors that can contribute to a slow HubSpot marketing website:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#1: You’ve not optimized images on your website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using too many or too large images on your HubSpot CMS can tremendously slow down your website. This is because, as you increase the number and the size of images on your website, load time increases which degrades the performance of your HubSpot website. Your website should have only the optimized images that have been presented in the correct format and are of the right size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you optimize images on your HubSpot Website? As a rule of thumb, always apply the following tips when creating images for your website:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always crop the images that you place on your website to the correct size. For instance, if your website page is 600px wide, then you should resize your images properly so that they fits that page width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduce the color depth of your images to the lowest acceptable levels of the color depth will affect the load times and performance on the client’s browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For photos use JPG as your preferred image file format. For storing line drawings, text, and iconic graphics at a smaller file size PNG is a better choice. Avoid using BMP and TIFF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#2: Unoptimized CSS or JavaScript&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your HubSpot website has a large code—it has additional spaces, line breaks, and indentations—then, you expect to have a slow website. If your CSS code has white spaces—which improves the readability of website code—then, there are high chances that it will slow down the performance of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should ensure that you compress your code to improve the performance of your website. If you want to compact your website code, you can GZIP your code. A GZIPed code significantly reduces the file size without affecting the images or video quality on your website. Here’s is how you can compact your website code:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always add the CSS and JavaScript to the external files as opposed to adding them inside your website This will ensure that these codes aren’t loaded wherever each page loads on a client browser, but they are only called whenever they’re required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always add the JS files to the footer of the web page where it’s possible. Placing the JS files at the footer of a web page ensures that they load in the background and don’t delay the web page that’s loading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look out for plugins that can compact the code on your HubSpot website. Tools such as YSlow—by Yahoo!, WebsiteTest.com—by Yottaa, Pingdom Website Speed Test can help you test the load times for your website to ensure its performance is within acceptable limits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#3: Lack of browser caching&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can reduce the load times for your website by storing commonly used website files—which include the html files, the CSS style sheets, the JavaScript scripts, as well as the graphic images— from your website on your clients’ browsers. In this case, you improve the load times by storing copies of your website images, your CSS, and JavaScript so that next time your client visits your website, his/her browser doesn’t have to load afresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that you should consider while using this feature is knowing the expiry time. Of course, the expiry time will depend on a couple of factors, chief among them being the different files that you’ll be caching and the restrictions that are defined by RFC’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#4: Lack of Plugin optimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a fact—plugins can help you to increase the functionalities of your HubSpot website. But too many plugins can slow down the performance of your website. In fact, if you use so many plugins that require many resources—such as the scripts and CSS—then such plugins are likely to perform complex operations that can degrade the performance of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, you should use plugins sparingly on your website only when they are necessary.  Otherwise, leave them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-bottom-line&#34;&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A slow website leads to losses of potential customers who’ll have brought in more loyal customers to your business. Therefore, you should always strive to improve the load times and performance of your website. To improve the load times and performance of your website—so that it’s not slow—you have to optimize the images, optimize the codes, optimize browser catching and finally use the plugins sparingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the only way that you’ll make your slow HubSpot website or blog to have a more conversion process from prospects into loyal customers. What’s your take? Keep us posted.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Forms for HubSpot</title>
      <link>https://integrationagent.com/smart-forms-installation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://integrationagent.com/smart-forms-installation</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;smart-forms-for-hubspot-can-help-you-increase-signup-conversion-by-17&#34;&gt;Smart Forms for HubSpot can help you increase signup conversion by 17%.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You probably know, that popup forms are very effective in terms of converting your visitors to subscribers, but at the same time they can be very annoying to users that can lead to a high bounce rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smart Forms provides a compromise of effective and user friendly way to increase forms conversion rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HubSpot native.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built specifically for HubSpot, you can use like any other module.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile ready&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slide in form, doesn&amp;#8217;t block content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timed based appearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a user closes the form – it wouldn&amp;#8217;t show up for the next 24 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a user submitted the form, the popup for this specific form will never be shown again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scroll-Based (in development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exit-Intent (in development)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/smart_forms.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-18 size-full&#34; src=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/smart_forms.png&#34; alt=&#34;smart_forms&#34; width=&#34;954&#34; height=&#34;692&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/smart_forms.png 954w, https://integrationagent.com/img/smart_forms-300x218.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/smart_forms-644x467.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 954px) 100vw, 954px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h3&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/SJQAtTi2B3Y&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To install Smart Forms and use it as HubSpot module you have to create a custom module first. Go to you HubSpot portal an then:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;padding-left: 30px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;em style=&#34;background-color: #f7f7b5;&#34;&gt;Content → Design Manager →  Custom Modules → New Custom Module&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;padding-left: 30px;&#34;&gt;
  Name it as &amp;#8220;Smart Forms&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Then to control your forms we need to add 3 text fields: &lt;strong&gt;Form Id&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt;Title&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Trigger Time.&lt;/strong&gt; Make sure to use the same names.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;padding-left: 30px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/new_field.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone wp-image-16 size-full&#34; src=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/new_field.png&#34; alt=&#34;new_field&#34; width=&#34;730&#34; height=&#34;624&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/new_field.png 730w, https://integrationagent.com/img/new_field-300x256.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/new_field-644x550.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 730px) 100vw, 730px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copy this code into the module body:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;pre class=&#34;theme:github font-size:14 inline-margin:10 lang:default decode:true &#34;&gt;&amp;lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; type=&#34;text/css&#34; href=&#34;https://integrationagent.s3.amazonaws.com/smartforms/smartforms.min.css&#34; /&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;script charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;//js.hsforms.net/forms/v2.js&#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;script src=&#34;https://integrationagent.s3.amazonaws.com/smartforms/smartforms.min.js&#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;
    $(document).ready( function() {
        HSPopup.init({
            formId: &#39;{{widget.form_id}}&#39;,
            portalId: &#39;{{ hub_id }}&#39;,
            title: &#39;{{widget.title}}&#39;,
            triggerTime: &#39;{{widget.trigger_time}}&#39;
        });

        HSPopup.showPopup();
    });
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;img src=&#34;https://integrationagent.s3.amazonaws.com/img/smart_forms.png&#34; class=&#34;smart_forms_logo&#34; /&amp;gt;

&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The module will look like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-17 size-full&#34; src=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/custom_module.png&#34; alt=&#34;custom_module&#34; width=&#34;1283&#34; height=&#34;413&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/custom_module.png 1283w, https://integrationagent.com/img/custom_module-300x97.png 300w, https://integrationagent.com/img/custom_module-644x207.png 644w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1283px) 100vw, 1283px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;to-add-the-module-to-a-page&#34;&gt;To add the module to a page&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drag and drop &amp;#8220;Smart Forms&amp;#8221; module to any place on the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/module2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-20 size-full&#34; src=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/module2.png&#34; alt=&#34;module2&#34; width=&#34;359&#34; height=&#34;409&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/module2.png 359w, https://integrationagent.com/img/module2-263x300.png 263w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 359px) 100vw, 359px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let&amp;#8217;s click on edit button and configure the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter wp-image-19 size-full&#34; src=&#34;http://intagent.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/module3.png&#34; alt=&#34;module3&#34; width=&#34;527&#34; height=&#34;415&#34; srcset=&#34;https://integrationagent.com/img/module3.png 527w, https://integrationagent.com/img/module3-300x236.png 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 527px) 100vw, 527px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Form Id: &lt;/strong&gt;Id of the HubSpot form you want to embed, to get the Id, open form editor and copy id from the url, e.g.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://app.hubspot.com/forms/1670983/&#34;&gt;https://app.hubspot.com/forms/1670983/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: #f7f7b5; text-decoration: underline&#34;&gt;c3794ad3-f6a7-4c98-841d-98062636baab&lt;/span&gt;/edit/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title&lt;/strong&gt;: The text that will be shown as form header.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger Time&lt;/strong&gt;: Time in seconds for the form to appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#8217;s it, in our case the form will show up in 30 seconds, it will automatically disappear after form completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;to-add-the-module-to-a-template&#34;&gt;To add the module to a template&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drag and drop &amp;#8220;HubL Template&amp;#8221; module to any spot on the template, modify the options with the following code:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre class=&#34;lang:default decode:true &#34;&gt;{% custom_widget &#34;smart_forms_widget&#34; widget_name=&#39;Smart Forms&#39; form_id=&#39;[FORM_ID]&#39;, title=&#39;[TITLE]&#39;, trigger_time=&#39;[SECONDS]&#39; %}&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>